<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SMP Diesel </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SMP Diesel </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>SMP Diesel 2025</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 11:22:16 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First Mahindra Dealer to Synchronize Two 200kVA Diesel Generators in South India in CPCB 4&#43;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/sync-200kva-dg-skylark/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/sync-200kva-dg-skylark/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SMP Diesel has achieved a groundbreaking feat by becoming the first Mahindra Sales Dealer in South India to successfully synchronize two 200kVA diesel generators in CPCB 4+ at the prestigious Skylark Estate Apartments,Hoodi Bengaluru. This remarkable achievement sets a new benchmark for the industry and showcases SMP Diesel&amp;rsquo;s technical expertise.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genuine Generator Parts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/products/genuine-parts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/products/genuine-parts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SMP Diesel, catering to the needs of customers who require authentic and reliable components for their generators, including Mahindra Powerol, Kirloskar and Cummins.&#xA;There’s a genuine difference in the performance, reliability, durability and value of engine parts. That’s why it always pays to go with the best.&#xA;We offer new parts,engine oil, overhauls parts and parts kit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TurnKey Installation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/products/turnkey-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/products/turnkey-installation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;powering-your-vision-from-concept-to-completion-smp-diesel-delivers-bespoke-turnkey-solutions-for-diesel-generators-expertly-crafting-every-detail---from-custom-tanks-to-amf-panel-boards---and-bringing-it-all-to-life-with-seamless-installation-erection-and-commissioning&#34;&gt;Powering Your Vision, From Concept to Completion. SMP Diesel delivers bespoke turnkey solutions for diesel generators, expertly crafting every detail - from custom tanks to AMF panel boards - and bringing it all to life with seamless installation, erection, and commissioning&lt;/h2&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10-25KVA Mahindra Powerol</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/products/10-25kva-mahindra/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/products/10-25kva-mahindra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;10 kVA, 15 kVA, and 25 kVA models, are highly sought after in commercial domains for quick backup power solutions. These generators are designed to provide reliable and efficient power, making them ideal for various applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>125-180KVA Mahindra Powerol</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/products/125-180kva-mahindra/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/products/125-180kva-mahindra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;125 kVA, 160 kVA, and 180 kVA models, are designed to provide reliable and efficient power for various applications. These generators are ideal for large commercial and industrial settings, such as data centers, hospitals, and manufacturing facilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200-320KVA Mahindra Powerol</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/products/200-320kva-mahindra/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/products/200-320kva-mahindra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;200 kVA, 250 kVA, and 320 kVA models, are designed to provide reliable and efficient power for various applications. These generators are ideal for large commercial and industrial settings, such as data centers, hospitals, and manufacturing facilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30-45KVA Mahindra Powerol</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/products/30-45kva-mahindra/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/products/30-45kva-mahindra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;30 kVA, 35 kVA, and 45 kVA models, are ideal for bungalows, small offices, and small shops. These generators are designed to provide reliable and efficient power, making them perfect for various applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400-625KVA Mahindra Powerol</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/products/400-625kva-mahindra/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/products/400-625kva-mahindra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;400 kVA, 500 kVA, and 625 kVA models, are designed to provide reliable and efficient power for various applications. These generators are ideal for large commercial and industrial settings, such as data centers, hospitals, and manufacturing facilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50-100KVA Mahindra Powerol</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/products/50-100kva-mahindra/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/products/50-100kva-mahindra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;50 kVA, 62.5 kVA, 82.5 kVA, and 100 kVA models, are designed to provide reliable and efficient power for various applications. These generators are ideal for large commercial and industrial settings, such as data centers, hospitals, and manufacturing facilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5KVA Mahindra Powerol</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/products/5kva-mahindra/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/products/5kva-mahindra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;compact-design&#34;&gt;Compact Design&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Compact design, allowing for a smooth transition to backup power. Additionally, its advanced governing system effectively regulates voltage fluctuations, ensuring the complete protection and safety of your equipment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Us and our Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/about-us-and-our-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/about-us-and-our-services/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SMP Diesel is a leading organization based in Bengaluru, India, specializing in diesel generators ranging from 10kVA to 1010kVA. With a proven track record, we have established ourselves as one of the premier generator dealers in Karnataka. Our commitment to quality, reliability, and customer satisfaction has earned us a reputation as the go-to source for all your diesel generator needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts in Diesel Generator Solutions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/experts-in-diesel-generator-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/experts-in-diesel-generator-solutions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to SMP Diesel, a leading provider of comprehensive diesel generator sales,services &amp;amp; rentals. With years of industry experience, we specialize in delivering top-notch solutions for all your generator needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
